Let's do this with Lohawat and the
reason for the surge of around 9% in ICC Lover today is that the board of ICC Bank has
given its approval to increase its stock, around 48%,
which we will increase to 50% and
due to this we are seeing a good surge in the stock, around 9%
is easy, Kshitij ICC people,
just look at its chart today, there will be a big
boom, how is the picture looking in the future,
first of all a very good greeting to you and see
here if we
talk about the market, then a good gap opening has been seen in the stock
and where
if we talk about the volume here, then a lot of
volume is being seen,
see here if
we talk about the chart setup, then the technical stock has
built up a base at a lower level and
after building up the base, a big
breakout was seen, in today's session the
base buildup in the Do sign in the stock was
in the range of 1130 to 1000 50
and after such a big consolidation  After a good
gap opening and good bidding, a
rise was seen in the stock here.
I think that in the coming enemy, this rise that has happened today
should continue in the stock because the overall setup is
showing a lot of positive from it. Here we are saying that we should
accumulate on the TIPS in the stock. Because overall I think that as long as the
stock is
exchanging above the level of 1140, there is a potential for such stock
flow and straightly move till 1300.
Gears of 8 to 8:30 are already being seen here in the stock,
so it is being said that on the nick of the heads, the
stock can be accumulated on the right side.
Right now the stock is rating 1190
1195. Arrange the stop loss till 1160 on the right side.
Maintain the stop loss below 1130
in the prefix as I told,
you can expect the level of 1300 in the stock.